I am a creative director and project manager with over 15 years of experience in the Printing industry. Utilizing my business acumen and creativity, I produce smart, unique marketing campaigns and designs. No matter the medium, I aim to create memorable, thoughtful communications.

EDUCATION

Front End Web Development Albany Can Code, Spring 2020

Master of Business Administration University at Albany

Bachelor of Arts
University at Albany
Concentration in Printmaking

PROFICIENCIES

HTML5/CSS
Adobe Creative Suite
Google Ads
Google Analytics
Unbounce
Facebook Business Manager
Facebook Ads Manager
Campaign Monitor
Digital Printing
Offset Printing
Large Format Printing
Direct Mail
USPS Mailing Requirements

OTHER

Secretary, Board of Directors Interfaith Partnership for the Homeless

Committee Member 2019-2020 TimesUnion.com/Table Hopping Mac & Cheese Bowl

EXPERIENCE

Creative Director and Department Coordinator Digital XPress *December 2016–October 2020*

Managed all marketing and creative projects for in-house creative agency, including estimating and scheduling; developed and implemented marketing campaigns for internal and external clients; art direction, branding and graphic design. Supervised and scheduled projects for team of four.

- Identified and eliminated inefficiencies to streamline interdepartmental procedures and increase productivity.
- Regularly conducted site surveys and executed project mockups for Large Format projects/installations (POP signage, interior décor, vehicle wraps).
- Developed and coordinated program to provide cranial band wraps for local children with plagiocephaly (Noodle Doodles, noodle.dxp1.com).
- Researched & oversaw implementation of web-to-print platform for B2C online store.

Project Coordinator Digital XPress January 2013-December 2016

- Managed print and mailing projects for dedicated customer accounts from bid through completion.
- Supported sales team in pricing, design, and implementation of direct mail campaigns to meet customer goals while maximizing profitability.

Customer Service Representative IBT/Hamilton 2009-January 2013

- Received, processed, tracked, and troubleshot projects through completion for dedicated customer accounts.
- Assisted with testing and development of automated processing workflow to reduce front end scheduling delays.
- Worked with sales, production, and customer to develop prescheduling procedures in an effort to reduce material delays internally; provided weekly reports to customer to assist with external scheduling and deadline requirements.
- Supported production across multiple manufacturing sites.

POD Prepress and Customer Service IBT Global 2006-2009